在这个讲座中，我们将讨论机器人手臂。
In this lecture, we are going to talk about robot arms.
特别是，我们将讨论机器人关节之间的关系
In particular, we are going to talk about the relationship between the joints in a robot's
手臂和机器人末端执行器的姿势。
arm and the pose of the robot end effector.
因此，当我用自己的手臂移动各种关节时，我们可以说是结束的姿势
So as I've moved the various joints in my own arm we can say that the pose of the end
我的手臂变了，对吗？
of my arm changes, right?
所以我们要做的是如何对通常包含的机器人手臂起作用
So what we're going to do is how this works for a robot arm which typically comprises
一些关节。
a number of joints.
在机器人的手臂中，它们变化，它们具有不同数量的关节，一些机器人手臂可能具有
In a robot's arm, they vary, they have different numbers of joints, some robot arms might have
只有3个关节，一些机器人手臂可能有6个关节，有些可能有10个关节，可能有
only 3 joints, some robot arms might have 6 joints and some might have 10 joints, could have
100个关节。
a 100 joints.
机器人手臂还有两种不同类型的关节。
There are also two different sorts of joints that robot arms have.
有些关节被称为棱柱关节。
There are joints that are called Prismatic joints.
这些是滑动或伸长的关节。
These are joints that slide or elongate.
并且有关节是旋转关节，就像我自己手臂上的关节一样。
And there are joints that are rotating joints, like the joints that I have in my own arm.
所以我们称这种旋转关节为旋转关节和滑动或伸缩
So we call these sort of rotating joints Revolute joints and the sliding or telescoping
我们称之为棱柱关节。
joints we called Prismatic joints.
因此，这里有一些存在的不同类型的机器人手臂的照片。
So here are some pictures of a number of different types of robot arms that exist.
这只是存在于其中的非常大量机器人手臂的非常小的样本
This is just a very small sample of a very very large number of robot arms that exist within
世界。
the world.
我们将研究其中的一些示例，查看它们，查看数字
We are going to work through some of these examples, look at them, look at the number
他们拥有的关节，他们拥有的不同类型的关节，然后继续工作
of joints that they have, the different types of joints that they have and then work on
数学描述，关节角度与数学关系
the mathematical description, the mathematical relationship between the joint angles and
机器人末端效应器的姿势。
the robot end effector pose.